Hi, I'm, uh, Monish Pare and I first met,
uh, Jack Skiing in 1999 when a group, us group of US YPOers,
uh, had him come to our retreat and he created what,
uh, I call the owner's manual, uh, for each of us.
And, uh, now Jack calls it the, the roadmap. Uh, but, uh,
I was, uh, quite unhappy, uh,
running, uh, my IT services system,
immigration company that I had founded about nine
years ago. And, uh, to the point that I didn't even wanna go to work,
the company had grown a lot, grown a lot, 170 people, uh,
and I hated it. And, uh, Jack, uh, did,
uh, 360 interviews with, uh,
my family spouse as well as gave,
gave me a bunch of, uh, tests to do.
And the end result was that he told me that it was a complete mismatch for me
to be running the business. Uh,
Jack told me that I was basically a guy who liked to play games,
but not just any games.
I preferred playing single player games that I
knew I had some edge to win. And, uh,
that was a incredible insight. And, uh,
right around then I was thinking of starting pry funds and he looked at it and
said that this would just be perfect for me. And, uh, it's been great. Um,
and, uh, I refer to my roadmap, uh,
every year and it's been really a life changer.
And I think everybody, uh,
should have a roadmap so they kind of know what, uh,
who they are and how they can maximize their
happiness and their productivity and, uh, effectiveness. And,
uh, so, uh, I think it's a no-brainer to, uh,
get with Jack and get that done. And I wish you all the best in your journey.
Thank you.